<resources>
    <string name="app_name">The Band Database</string>
    <string name="details">Details</string>

    <string-array name="bands">
        <item>The Beatles</item>
        <item>Nirvana</item>
        <item>U2</item>
        <item>XXXTentacion</item>
        <item>Lil Peep</item>
        <item>Juice WRLD</item>
        <item>NF</item>
        <item>21 Savage</item>
        <item>bbno$</item>
        <item>Yung Gravy</item>
        <item>Khantrast</item>
        <item>Jon Bellion</item>
        <item>Connor Price</item>
        <item>Polyphia</item>
        <item>TOKYO\'S REVENGE</item>
        <item>CORPSE</item>
        <item>24kGoldn</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="descriptions">
        <item>An English rock band that formed in Liverpool in 1960.</item>
        <item>An American rock band that formed in Washington in 1987.</item>
        <item>An Irish rock band from Dublin that formed in 1976.</item>
        <item>Rap artist referred to as \'X\' who took influence from many artists outside of rap. Widely known for his public legal troubles </item>
        <item>Swedish-American rapper, singer, and songwriter. He was a member of the emo rap collective GothBoiClique.</item>
        <item>He was a leading figure in the emo rap and SoundCloud rap genres. Could still be alive</item>
        <item>Christian rapper who discusses mental health problems</item>
        <item>British rapper based in Atlanta, Georgia, United States</item>
        <item>Canadian rapper and singer from Vancouver. He is best known for his 2019 single "Lalala" with producer Y2K</item>
        <item>Mr. Clean</item>
        <item>Anime themed rapper who gained a following on youtube</item>
        <item>He is best known for his song "All Time Low," along with his writing and producing credits. Bellion has released four mixtapes and two studio albums. </item>
        <item>Canadian-American actor and hip hop artist. Beginning his career as a child actor, he is best known for his roles in the films Cinderella Man and Good Luck Chuck.</item>
        <item>Instrumental metal band that has blown up over the last couple years</item>
        <item>American rapper. He rose to fame with the songs "GoodMorningTokyo!" and "Thot!", both going viral on TikTok and amassing millions of videos on the platform.</item>
        <item>Internet personality Corpse Husband</item>
        <item>American rapper and singer. In 2019, he rose to fame with his single, "Valentino", peaking at number 92 on the US Billboard Hot 100.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>